<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>THE PROVERBIAL NINJA CODE &lt;/&gt;</title>
  <subtitle></subtitle>
  <link href="https://blog.proverbial.ninja/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.proverbial.ninja/"/>
  
    <updated>2023-07-10T21:00:00+03:00</updated>
  
  <id>https://blog.proverbial.ninja</id>
  <author>
    <name>Proverbial Ninja</name>
    <email>me@proverbial.ninja</email>
  </author>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>Flooperman v0.1.0 A Work-in-Progress Looperman Client</title>
      <link href="https://blog.proverbial.ninja/posts/flooperman-v0.1.0-a-work-in-progress-looperman-client/"/>
      <updated>2023-07-10T21:00:00+03:00</updated>
      <id>https://blog.proverbial.ninja/posts/flooperman-v0.1.0-a-work-in-progress-looperman-client/</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
      <h2>Flooperman v0.1.0: A Work-in-Progress Looperman Client</h2>
<p><img src="/images/flooperman.png" alt="flooperman screenshot"></p>
<p>I'm excited to announce the release of Flooperman v0.1.0, a work-in-progress client for Looperman. This version of Flooperman is not meant for public release, as it is still under development and has some bugs. However, it covers the following requirements that I needed in order to put it to use immediately:</p>
<p>I also have a GIF demonstrating how Flooperman works, which I'll include at the end of this blog post.</p>
<p><strong>Features</strong></p>
<p>Here are some of the features of Flooperman v0.1.0:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>List Looperman homepage loops:</strong> Flooperman can list the loops that are currently featured on the Looperman homepage. This is a great way to find new loops to use in your music production.</li>
<li><strong>Play loops:</strong> Flooperman can play loops straight from Looperman. This is a great way to preview loops before you download them.</li>
<li><strong>Download loops:</strong> Flooperman can download loops from Looperman. This is a great way to save loops for offline use.</li>
<li><strong>Show downloads:</strong> Flooperman can show a list of all the loops that you have downloaded. This is a great way to keep track of your loops.</li>
<li><strong>Edit ID3 tags:</strong> Flooperman can edit the ID3 tags of loops. This is a great way to add metadata to your loops.</li>
<li><strong>Drag loops into DAW:</strong> Flooperman can drag loops into a DAW. This is a great way to import loops into your music production software.</li>
<li><strong>Keyword search:</strong> Flooperman can search for loops by keyword. This is a great way to find specific loops that you're looking for.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Bugs</strong></p>
<p>There are a few bugs in Flooperman v0.1.0. These bugs include:</p>
<ul>
<li>The play button sometimes doesn't work.</li>
<li>No visual indication of downloads.</li>
<li>Improved parsing of the data from</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Future Plans</strong></p>
<p>I'm planning to release a new version of Flooperman soon. This new version will include the following features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Improved UI</li>
<li>Better state management</li>
<li>Pagination for the home and search pages</li>
<li>More bug fixes</li>
</ul>
<p>I'm also planning to add the following features to Flooperman in the future:</p>
<ul>
<li>Advanced search (by bpm, genre, key etc).</li>
<li>Ability to favourite/categorize loops.</li>
<li>The ability to share loops with other users</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>GIF Demonstration</strong></p>
<p>Here is a GIF demonstrating how Flooperman works:</p>
<p><img src="/images/flooperman2.gif" alt="flooperman at work"></p>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>Flooperman v0.1.0 is a work-in-progress, but it's a great way to find, download, and use loops from Looperman. I'm excited to release a new version of Flooperman soon with more features and bug fixes.
Version 0.2.0 of Flooperman will have an improved UI, better state management, and pagination for the home and search pages.</p>
<p><strong>Thanks for reading!</strong></p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
</feed>